# **WONG HAU CHENG**

ELECTRONIC & COMPUTER ENGINEERING STUDENT

### **PROFILE**

A diligent and outgoing 22-year old Engineering student from Ngee Ann Polytechnic. Aspiring to have a career as a Software Engineer, I am not afraid to expand my knowledge in Software Engineering by being open-minded and exposing myself to different areas as well. My personal goal is to have a career I can be proud of when I look back upon my achievements and to be able to provide for my family.

# CONTACT

Mobile: +65 9398 3576

E-mail: S10194108@connect.np.edu.sg Address: Jurong West Street 61, BLK

, taar eest var en 6 11 eet et eet e 1,

651B #14-362 S(642651)

# EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN ELECTRONIC
 & COMPUTER
 ENGINEERING | NGEE
 ANN POLYTECHNIC

2019 - 2023

• GCE 'N' LEVEL | JURONG WEST SECONDARY SCHOOL

2014 - 2018

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### INTERNSHIP AT CREATIVE TECHNLOGY

Tester | Mar 2022 - August 2022

- Identify, document, and track software defects using defect tracking tools.
- Generating test reports and providing insights of the quality of Software
- Support supervisors with firmware/hardware updates
- Work closely with the development team to resolve issues and verify fixes.
- Collaborating with developers and managers to reach quality goals and requirements.

#### SGUNITED PROMOTER

Awareness Ambassador | Aug 2020 - Sept 2020

- Raising awareness about a new government job website
- Answering queries

# **SKILLS**

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Interpersonal skills Open-minded Ownership Fast Learner Self-developmental

#### HARD SKILLS

C and C# Language
Programming
Cloud Computing (AWS)
Microsoft Office Suite
Tinkercad
EagleCad
Arduino
Linux Virtual Box (VM)
Soldering
MiniTab
Python
HTML/CSS/Javascript

## **CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

## **BASKETBALL CLUB**

Jurong West Secondary School | 2017 - 2019

- Represented team to compete in B-Division Basketball
- Participated actively in basketball camps
- Trained vigorously every week

## **RED CROSS YOUTH**

Cadet | 2015 - 2017

- Awarded Best Cadet of the Month 2016
- Represented batch to march for the prestigious Speech Day
- Attended and participated all camps

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

#### **RED CROSS YOUTH**

Fundraiser | 2016 - 2017

• Fund-raised for beneficiaries